<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Điện cơ Thanh Hiền</title>
    <link>https://dalafarm.vn/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Điện cơ Thanh Hiền</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>vi-vn</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 23:12:45 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://dalafarm.vn/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Extra virgin garlic-infused sesame oil (250ml)</title>
      <link>https://dalafarm.vn/en/product/extra-virgin-garlic-infused-sesame-oil-250ml/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 23:12:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dalafarm.vn/en/product/extra-virgin-garlic-infused-sesame-oil-250ml/</guid>
      <description>EXTRA VIRGIN GARLIC-INFUSED SESAME OIL Ingredients 100% garlic-infused sesame oil. No additives or preservatives
Why eat baby oil? Cooking oil is a very important nutrient group, which plays a major role in providing energy to children. Particularly unsaturated fats such as omega-3, which make up 60% of the brain&amp;rsquo;s essential nutrients, help the brain control behaviors, enhance memory and cognition.
Fat also helps to form fat tissue that regulates body heat, providing fat to help the process of absorbing important vitamins in the body (A, D, E, K), &amp;hellip; the use of fatty substances It is very important to be sensible with the body of the child.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DalaBaby Vegetables Powder (70g)</title>
      <link>https://dalafarm.vn/en/product/dalababy-vegetables-powder-70g/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 23:12:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dalafarm.vn/en/product/dalababy-vegetables-powder-70g/</guid>
      <description>DalaBaby Vegetables Powder DalaBaby Vegetables Powder is carefully picked and processed from the most fresh and best raw vegetables grown in our own farm in Lam Dong. Our products are produced by SEFD technology (patent pending) and is certified by Vietnam Food Safety regulator.
According to the World Health Organization&amp;rsquo;s recommendations, each baby should consume 300 - 400 grams of vegetables perday.
With Điện cơ Thanh Hiền Vegetables Powder, 3-5 grams of powder is equivalent to 80 - 100 grams of fresh vegetables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Purple Sweet Potato Powder (50g)</title>
      <link>https://dalafarm.vn/en/product/purple-sweet-potato-powder-50g/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2017 08:05:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dalafarm.vn/en/product/purple-sweet-potato-powder-50g/</guid>
      <description>Điện cơ Thanh Hiền Purple Sweet Potato powder Điện cơ Thanh Hiền Purple Sweet Potato powder is carefully picked and processed from the most fresh and best raw vegetables grown in our own farm in Lam Dong. Our products are produced by SEFD technology (patent pending) and is certified by Vietnam Food Safety regulator.
Ingredients: 100% Purple Sweet Potato No flavor or additive added
Benefits: Rich in carbohydrates, fiber, beta-carotene (vitamin A carotenoids), vitamin C, vitamin B6, iron, manganese and potassium.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spinach Powder (50g)</title>
      <link>https://dalafarm.vn/en/product/spinach-powder-50g/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2017 08:05:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dalafarm.vn/en/product/spinach-powder-50g/</guid>
      <description>Điện cơ Thanh Hiền Spinach Powder Điện cơ Thanh Hiền Spinach powder is carefully picked and processed from the most fresh and best raw vegetables grown in our own farm in Lam Dong. Our products are produced by SEFD technology (patent pending) and is certified by Vietnam Food Safety regulator.
Ingredients: 100% Spinach No flavor or additive added
Benefits: Spinach is rich in vitamin K, A, E, B2, B6, B1, C, manganese, magnesium, iron, calcium, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beetroot powder (50g)</title>
      <link>https://dalafarm.vn/en/product/beetroot-powder-50g/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 23:12:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dalafarm.vn/en/product/beetroot-powder-50g/</guid>
      <description>Beetroot powder Điện cơ Thanh Hiền beetroot powder is carefully picked and processed from the most fresh and best raw vegetables grown in our own farm in Lam Dong. Our products are produced by SEFD technology (patent pending) and is certified by Vietnam Food Safety regulator.
Ingredients: 100% Beetroot No flavor or additive added
Benefits: Beetroot is rich in vitamins A, C, B9, iron, potassium, magnesium, folic acid, betaine, zinc and phosphate, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Broccoli powder (50g)</title>
      <link>https://dalafarm.vn/en/product/broccoli-powder-50g/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 23:12:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dalafarm.vn/en/product/broccoli-powder-50g/</guid>
      <description>Broccoli powder Điện cơ Thanh Hiền broccoli powder is carefully picked and processed from the most fresh and best raw vegetables grown in our own farm in Lam Dong. Our products are produced by SEFD technology (patent pending) and is certified by Vietnam Food Safety regulator.
Ingredients: 100% Broccoli No flavor or additive added
Benefits: Broccoli contains powerful antioxidants which is good for the heart, reduce in flammation, lower blood pressure, reduce cholesterol levels, minimize signs of aging and boost the immune system function.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carrot powder (50g)</title>
      <link>https://dalafarm.vn/en/product/carrot-powder-50g/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 23:12:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dalafarm.vn/en/product/carrot-powder-50g/</guid>
      <description>Carrot powder Điện cơ Thanh Hiền Carrot powder is carefully picked and processed from the most fresh and best raw vegetables grown in our own farm in Lam Dong. Our products are produced by SEFD technology (patent pending) and is certified by Vietnam Food Safety regulator.
Ingredients: 100% Carrot No flavor or additive added
Benefits: Carrot improves eye vision, lowers the risk for stroke, chronic diseases, including cancer and cardiovascular disease.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heartleaf powder (100g)</title>
      <link>https://dalafarm.vn/en/product/heartleaf-powder-100g/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 23:12:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dalafarm.vn/en/product/heartleaf-powder-100g/</guid>
      <description>Heartleaf powder Điện cơ Thanh Hiền Heartleaf powder is carefully picked and processed from the most fresh and best raw vegetables grown in our own farm in Lam Dong. Our products are produced by SEFD technology (patent pending) and is certified by Vietnam Food Safety regulator.
Ingredients: 100% Heartleaf No flavor or additive added
Benefits: Heartleaf has laxative and anti- inflammatory properties. It is a rich source of vitamins C, E, G, K, choline and minerals which aid detoxifying your body, digestion and treating hemorrhoids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heartleaf powder (50g)</title>
      <link>https://dalafarm.vn/en/product/heartleaf-powder-50g/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 23:12:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dalafarm.vn/en/product/heartleaf-powder-50g/</guid>
      <description>Heartleaf powder Điện cơ Thanh Hiền Heartleaf powder is carefully picked and processed from the most fresh and best raw vegetables grown in our own farm in Lam Dong. Our products are produced by SEFD technology (patent pending) and is certified by Vietnam Food Safety regulator.
Ingredients: 100% Heartleaf No flavor or additive added
Benefits: Heartleaf has laxative and anti- inflammatory properties. It is a rich source of vitamins C, E, G, K, choline and minerals which aid detoxifying your body, digestion and treating hemorrhoids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moringa powder (50g)</title>
      <link>https://dalafarm.vn/en/product/moringa-powder-50g/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 23:12:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dalafarm.vn/en/product/moringa-powder-50g/</guid>
      <description>Moringa powder Điện cơ Thanh Hiền Moringa powder is carefully picked and processed from the most fresh and best raw vegetables grown in our own farm in Lam Dong. Our products are produced by SEFD technology (patent pending) and is certified by Vietnam Food Safety regulator.
Ingredients: 100% Moringa No flavor or additive added
Benefits: Moringa contains around 20 types of amino-acids, 46 antioxidants, 36 anti- inflammatory compounds and more than 90 nutrients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pennywort powder (100g)</title>
      <link>https://dalafarm.vn/en/product/pennywort-powder-100g/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 23:12:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dalafarm.vn/en/product/pennywort-powder-100g/</guid>
      <description>Pennywort powder Điện cơ Thanh Hiền Pennywort powder is carefully picked and processed from the most fresh and best raw vegetables grown in our own farm in Lam Dong. Our products are produced by SEFD technology (patent pending) and is certified by Vietnam Food Safety regulator.
Ingredients: 100% Pennywort No flavor or additive added
Benefits: Pennywort is rich in vitamins, minerals and other nutrition such as beta carotene, sterols to reduce cholesterol absorption and promote skin cell regeneration process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pennywort powder (50g)</title>
      <link>https://dalafarm.vn/en/product/pennywort-powder-50g/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 23:12:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dalafarm.vn/en/product/pennywort-powder-50g/</guid>
      <description>Pennywort powder Điện cơ Thanh Hiền Pennywort powder is carefully picked and processed from the most fresh and best raw vegetables grown in our own farm in Lam Dong. Our products are produced by SEFD technology (patent pending) and is certified by Vietnam Food Safety regulator.
Ingredients: 100% Pennywort No flavor or additive added
Benefits: Pennywort is rich in vitamins, minerals and other nutrition such as beta carotene, sterols to reduce cholesterol absorption and promote skin cell regeneration process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pumpkin powder (50g)</title>
      <link>https://dalafarm.vn/en/product/pumpkin-powder-50g/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 23:12:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dalafarm.vn/en/product/pumpkin-powder-50g/</guid>
      <description>Pumpkin powder Điện cơ Thanh Hiền Pumpkin powder is carefully picked and processed from the most fresh and best raw vegetables grown in our own farm in Lam Dong. Our products are produced by SEFD technology (patent pending) and is certified by Vietnam Food Safety regulator.
Ingredients: 100% Pumpkin No flavor or additive added
Benefits: Pumpkin is rich in vital antioxidants, vitamins A, B6, C, E and beta-carotene have been shown to support eye health and prevent degenerative dam.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>