<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>dalababy-powder on Điện cơ Thanh Hiền</title>
    <link>https://dalafarm.vn/en/tags/dalababy-powder/</link>
    <description>Recent content in dalababy-powder on Điện cơ Thanh Hiền</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>vi-vn</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 23:12:45 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://dalafarm.vn/en/tags/dalababy-powder/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Extra virgin garlic-infused sesame oil (250ml)</title>
      <link>https://dalafarm.vn/en/product/extra-virgin-garlic-infused-sesame-oil-250ml/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 23:12:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dalafarm.vn/en/product/extra-virgin-garlic-infused-sesame-oil-250ml/</guid>
      <description>EXTRA VIRGIN GARLIC-INFUSED SESAME OIL Ingredients 100% garlic-infused sesame oil. No additives or preservatives
Why eat baby oil? Cooking oil is a very important nutrient group, which plays a major role in providing energy to children. Particularly unsaturated fats such as omega-3, which make up 60% of the brain&amp;rsquo;s essential nutrients, help the brain control behaviors, enhance memory and cognition.
Fat also helps to form fat tissue that regulates body heat, providing fat to help the process of absorbing important vitamins in the body (A, D, E, K), &amp;hellip; the use of fatty substances It is very important to be sensible with the body of the child.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DalaBaby Vegetables Powder (70g)</title>
      <link>https://dalafarm.vn/en/product/dalababy-vegetables-powder-70g/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 23:12:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dalafarm.vn/en/product/dalababy-vegetables-powder-70g/</guid>
      <description>DalaBaby Vegetables Powder DalaBaby Vegetables Powder is carefully picked and processed from the most fresh and best raw vegetables grown in our own farm in Lam Dong. Our products are produced by SEFD technology (patent pending) and is certified by Vietnam Food Safety regulator.
According to the World Health Organization&amp;rsquo;s recommendations, each baby should consume 300 - 400 grams of vegetables perday.
With Điện cơ Thanh Hiền Vegetables Powder, 3-5 grams of powder is equivalent to 80 - 100 grams of fresh vegetables.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>